Guide to the Irish Echo Photographs AIA.045
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Irish America, 1936-2004; 7.21 Linear Feet in 2 oversized flat boxes, 3 record cartons, 4 card boxes, and 1 manuscript box
  - Subseries I.C: Subjects, circa 1930-1936, 1967-2004.
    - Father John C. Drumgoole, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Eagle Tavern, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Education, 1974-1975, circa 1981-1997, undated (Box 15, Folder 1-6, Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Ellis Island, 1987-1988, circa 1995-1996, 2001, undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Erin's Isle Ballroom, circa 1930, circa 1936 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Events: A Day in the Bog, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Events: American: General, circa 1970s-1980s, 1990, 1994-2002, undated (Box 2, Folder 67, Box 15, Folder 7-8)
    - Events: American: Jeanie Johnson, circa 2000 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Events: Monaco Royal Family, undated (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Events: Unidentified, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Feis: General, 1989, 1994, circa 2000, undated (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Feis: Inis Fada Feis, 8th Annual, circa 2000 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Festivals: General, 1992, 1995, 2007-2008, undated (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Festivals: Great Irish Fair, circa 2000 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Festivals: Guinness Fleadh, undated (Box 15, Folder 12-19)
    - Festivals: Guinness Oyster Festival, circa 2000 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Festivals: New York Irish Festival, undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Fire Department, circa 1970s, 1987-1988, 2000, undated (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Florida, circa 1975, 1989, 1994-1995, undated (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Hibernia Magazine, undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Historic: Sites, Buildings, Personalities, circa 1970s-1980s, 1990-1997, 2001-2007, undated (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Historic Sites: Statue of Liberty, Unid Monument, Ellis Island, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Historic Sites: Rockefeller Center Christmas Tree, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Illinois (Chicago), 1988-1995, 2007, undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Immigration: General, circa 1960s-1970s, 1998-2002, undated (Box 2, Folder 74-75)
    - Immigration: Irish Chaplaincy, 1987, undated (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Irish Echo: 65th Anniversary Edition, 1993 (Oversize 22, Folder 3, Oversize 21, Folder 2)
    - Irish Language, 1988-1999, undated (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Irish Press Corporation, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Irish Radio and Television Programs, 1987-1988, circa 1992, undated (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Marches, Parades, Poltical Protests, Political Art, 1984, 1990-1992, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 5, Folder 9-11)
    - Marching Bands, 1992 (Oversize 21, Folder 3)
    - Massachusetts (Boston), circa 1970s-1980s, 1992-1995, undated (Box 2, Folder 80-81, Box 15, Folder 23-24)
    - McCormicks, undated (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Military/Veterans, circa 1969-1991, 1994-1995, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Military/Veterans - 69th Regiment Crest. Congressional Medal of Honor, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - New Jersey, 1969-1995, undated (Box 3, Folder 2-3, Box 15, Folder 25-26)
    - New York (Bronx), circa 1970s-1980s, 1993, 2001-2003, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - New York (Brooklyn): Colleen Queen, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - New York (Brooklyn): General, circa 1970s-1980s, 1990, 1994, circa 1999, undated (Box 15, Folder 27-28, Box 3, Folder 5-6)
    - New York (Brooklyn): Cardinal Newman Council Knights of Columbus, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - New York (Brooklyn): St. Raymond's Gaelic Athletic Association, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - New York (Catskills), circa 1970, 1977, 1982-1995, 2002-2004, undated (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
    - New York (Catskills) - Irish American Museum, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - New York (Manhattan): General, circa 1972, 1988, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - New York (Manhattan: Inwood), circa 1970, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - New York (Nassau County), circa 1975-1995, undated (Box 15, Folder 31-32, Box 3, Folder 11-12)
    - New York (Queens): General, circa 1970, 1975, 1986-1990, 1997, undated (Box 15, Folder 33-34, Box 3, Folder 13)
    - New York (Queens): Rockaway Irish Fair, undated (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - New York (Queens): Woodside, undated (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - New York (Queens): Woodside (Copperface Jack's Bar), undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - New York (Rockland County), 1971, 1975, 1982-1990, 2001-2002, undated (Box 15, Folder 37, Box 3, Folder 14)
    - New York (Staten Island), 1986-1988, 1996-2001, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - New York (Suffolk County), circa 1970s, 1988-1989, 1995-1996, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - New York (Westchester County), circa 1970s, 1982, 1987-1994, 2001-2002, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Pennsylvania: General, 1975-1982, 1988-1992, 1999-2000, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Pennsylvania: Guinness Weekend in the Poconos, undated (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Police, circa 1960s-1970s, 1982-1993, 2002, 2004, undated (Box 3, Folder 19, Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Police - Dennis Mulcahy, NYC Bomb Squad, undated (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Protest (Photo Negatives), undated (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Queens Calvary Cemetery, circa 1970s, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Queens Park Rangers (Photo Negatives), undated (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Rose of Tralee (and related), 1963, circa 1970s-1999, undated (Box 3, Folder 21, Oversize 22, Folder 4, Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Rose of Tralee (New York), 1990-1991 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Rose of Tralee: New York Darlin' Girl from Clare, circa 2000 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Rosie O'Grady's, undated (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - September 11th, 2001, 2002-2003, undated (Box 3, Folder 22, Box 15, Folder 41-42)
    - St. Patrick's Day Parade Committee (New York), circa 1960s-1994, 2000-2001, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - St. Patrick's Day Parade Grand Marshals, circa 1970-1979, 1986-1990, 2002-2003, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - St. Patrick's Day Parade (New York), circa 1970s, 1987-1996, 2001, 2003, undated (Box 15, Folder 43-49, Box 23, Folder 7, Folder 4, Box 16, Folder 1-3, Box 3, Folder 25-27, Oversize 22, Folder 5, Box 24, Folder 34)
    - St. Patrick's Day Parades (outside New York City), 1968-1976, 1983-2003, undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - St. Patrick's Old Cathedral (Mott Street), undated (Oversize 21, Folder 5)
    - Testimonial Dinner in Honor of William McFetridge, 1952 (Box Shared Tamiment 161, Folder 14)
    - Texas, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Thomas O'Reilly Memorial Banquet, Gaelic Athletic Association of Greater New York, 1963 (Box Shared Tamiment 161, Folder 14)
    - Tower View Ballroom (Queens), undated (Box 16, Folder 4, Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Trinity Ball, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Unidentified Social Events Contact Sheets, undated (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Washington, D.C., 1977, 1984-1998, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Weddings (United States), 1960, circa 1970s, 1981-1997, 2000-2004, undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - World's Fair: Irish Pavilion, 1963-1964, 1977, undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Subseries I.D: Sports, 1936, 1951-2001
    This subseries contains photographs of Irish sports in America. Extensive documentation of the Gaelic Athletic Association (GAA) and associated groups are complemented by coverage of hurling and soccer. Featured within this subseries is considerable photographic documentation of Gaelic Park from the 1950s through the 1990s.
    - Cu Culain (Chicago Hurling Team), undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Football Ladies Westmeath Ladies vs. Breffni Inn, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - GAA Ladies Football Unid Team, undated (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Gaelic Athletic Association (G.A.A.) (New York), 1967, 1972-1978, 1981-1994, 2001, undated (Box 3, Folder 35-36, Box 16, Folder 6-11, Box 29, Folder 1-2, Box 30)
    - Gaelic Athletic Association - NY vs. St. John's, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Gaelic Athletic Association - Practice, undated (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Gaelic Athletic Association - Unid Team Practice, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Gaelic Athletic League - Westmeath Junior Football, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Gaelic Football, undated (Box 16, Folder 12-16)
    - Gaelic Football (Donegal), undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Gaelic Games - Cavan Ladies Football Club, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Gaelic Games - Cavan Ladies G.F.C., 1993 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Gaelic Games (United States), undated (Box 3, Folder 37, Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Gaelic Minor Teams, 1984, 1987-1988, 1995, undated (Box 3, Folder 38, Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Gaelic Park (Bronx), 1951, 1968, circa 1970s, 1981-1995, undated (Box 3, Folder 39-40)
    - Horse/Dog Racing, 1991-1992, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 6-7)
    - Hurling/Camogie, 1936, 1966, 1982-1996, undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Sailing, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Sheridan, Martin, circa 1976, undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Sports (Contact Sheets), undated (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Sports - General, undated (Box 24, Folder 37, Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Sports (Photo Negatives), undated (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Soccer, circa 1976, circa 1987, 1993-2004, undated (Box 3, Folder 43, Box 16, Folder 18-19, Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Soccer: Bronx Irish Soccer League, undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Soccer: Queens Park Rangers vs. NY Rovers, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Soccer/Rugby/Hurling, 1984, 1990, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 3-4)
    - Tipperary Awards, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Unidentified Sports Award, undated (Box 33, Folder 29)
- Series II: Ireland, 1959-2004; 7.44 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons, 2 card boxes, 2 oversized flat boxes, and 3 manuscript boxes
  This series consists of photographic prints of various sizes, all of which were taken in The Republic of Ireland or Northern Ireland over a period of approximately 65 years. The photographs contained in this series document tourism and tourist attractions in almost all of the Irish counties; major Irish businesses and business leaders; Irish politicians; and Irish athletes and the athletic events. This series contains photographs documenting key aspects of Irish life and is further divided into four subseries.
  - Subseries II.A: Tourism, 1957-2003
    This subseries is comprised largely of scenic photographs taken in many of the Irish counties. Specific tourist destinations are organized by type, such as churches or pubs.
    - American Visitors in Ireland, 1969, circa 1970s, 1989-1996, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Ballyporeen, undated (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Castles, 1987-1988, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Churches, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Cliffs of Moher, 2006; TW_AIA_045_ER_4
    - Cottages, circa 1975, 1987, 1994-1999, undated (Box 4, Folder 4, Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Country Houses, 1975, 1995, 1997, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - County Antrim, 1987-1988, 1992, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - County Cavan, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - County Clare, 1974, circa 1977, 1988, 1996, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - County Cork, 1985, 1988, 1993, 1995, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - County Donegal, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 10, Box 30, Folder 30)
    - County Down, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - County Dublin, circa 1982, 1987-1997, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - County Galway, circa 1970s, 1982-1988, 1992 undated (Box 4, Folder 13, Box 30, Folder 32)
    - County Kerry, 1987-1988, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - County Kildare, 1987-1988, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - County Kilkenny, 1987, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - County Leitrim, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - County Limerick, 1993, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - County Longford, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - County Louth, 1988, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - County Mayo, circa 1970s, 1981-1992, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - County Meath, 1994, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - County Monaghan, 1994, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - County Offaly, 1988, 1994, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - County Sligo, 1987, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - County Tipperary, 1987, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - County Waterford, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - County Wexford, 1989, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - County Wicklow, 1987-1988, 1992, undated (Box 4, Folder 29, Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Derry, undated (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Dublin (Trinity Ball), 1972 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Dublin - Young Baskers on Grafton Street, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Farming, 1987, 1996-1997, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Fishing, 1997, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Historic, 1987, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Horses, 1994, 1996, undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Hotels, 1975, 1989, 1997, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Ireland, 1982, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Irish Tourist Board (Bord Failte), 1957, 1966, circa 1970s-1980s, 1995-1996, undated (Box 4, Folder 34-35, Oversize 21, Folder 6, Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Irish Travel Agents Association, undated (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Lake, undated (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Lismore Castle, Watford, undated (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Northern Ireland Tourist Board, 2000, undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Pubs, 1992, 1996-1997, undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Restored Synagogue, Jewish Museum - Dublin, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Scenic Ireland, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - Special Olympics, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - St. Patrick's Day Parade Dublin, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Tea at Restaurant, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Tourism, undated (Oversize 22, Folder 6, Box 20, Folder 1, Oversize 21, Folder 7, Box 34)
    - Tourism - Scenic, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 48)
    - Towns, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Various, 1971, 1982, 1986, 1992, 1994-1996 (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - Westport, Co. Mayo, undated (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Subseries II.B: Business, 1964-2003
    This subseries contains photographs of prominent Irish businesses and business leaders. Included in this subseries are numerous photographs of Aer Lingus/Irish International Airlines during the 1960s and 1970s. Also featured within this subseries are photographs of assorted smaller Irish businesses, which are featured in General Business folders.
    - Aer Lingus/Irish International Airlines: General, 1966-1967, circa 1970s-1992, 1999, 2003, undated (Box 4, Folder 39-41)
    - Allied/Star Management Team, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Claddagh Tea Set, undated (Box 24, Folder 51)
    - Corrigan, John, undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - DeLorean, John, undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - General Business, circa 1970s-1998, undated (Box 4, Folder 44-45, Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Guinness, undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Market, undated (Box 24, Folder 52)
    - McGuckian, John B., undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - O'Reilly, Tony, circa 1995 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Pot O'Gold, undated (Box 24, Folder 53)
    - Smurfit, Michael, 1992, 1995, undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Stephan Joyce, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - UNID Construction Site, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Subseries II.C: Politics, 1959-2004
    This subseries contains photographs of influential politicians from both the Republic of Ireland and Northern Ireland. Included in this subseries are Sinn Féin President Gerry Adams, former Social Democratic and Labour Party leader John Hume, Presidents of Ireland Éamon de Valera and Mary Robinson, and former Taoisigh Bertie Ahern and Séan Lemass. Other noteworthy individuals appearing in this series include former British Prime Ministers Tony Blair and Margaret Thatcher.
    Arrangement
    This subseries features images of Irish politicians organized alphabetically by surname; minor politicians, as well as prominent politicians with limited documentation, are featured in the alphabetic sequence prefaced by "Individual Politicians" and followed by a letter.
    - Adams, Gerry, 1992-1997, 2004, undated (Box 4, Folder 47, Box 25, Folder 1-3, Box 30, Folder 41, Box 32, Folder 36)
      Scope and Contents
      Some of the photographs of Gerry Adams also feature John F. Kennedy Jr., John Hume MP, and Taoiseach Bertie Aherns.
    - Ahern, Bertie, 1992-1997, 2003, undated (Box 4, Folder 48, Box 30, Folder 40)
    - Ahern, Bertie - Memorial Service, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Alderice, John, 1996, undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Blair, Tony, 1994-1995, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Blaney, Neil, undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Briscoe, Ben, undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Brooke, Peter, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Bruton, John, 1991, 1995-1997, undated (Box 4, Folder 54, Oversize 22, Folder 7)
    - Cahill, Joe, 1995-1996, undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Childers, Erskine, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Collins, Gerry, 1984, 1990-1991, undated (Box 4, Folder 57, Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Collins, Steve, 1995, undated (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Conlon, Gerry, circa 1990 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Coogan, Tim Pat, 1991-1992, undated (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Corrigan, Mairead, undated (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Cosgrave, Liam, undated (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Costello, Darina, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Costello, Declan, undated (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Cowen, Brian, 2003, undated (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Currie, Austin, undated (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - DeRosa, Peter, undated (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - DeRossa, Proinsias, 1991-1997, undated (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Desmond, Dermot, undated (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - DeValera, Eamon, circa 1960s, 1989, undated (Box 4, Folder 69, Box 25, Folder 4)
    - DeValera, Sile, undated (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Doherty, Pat, 1994, 1996, undated (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Donnelly, Michael (Lord Mayor of Dublin), undated (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Dukes, Allen, undated (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Ferris, Martin, undated (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Finlay, Fergus, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Finley, Thomas (Chief Justice), 1992 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Fitzgerald, Desmond, undated (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Fitzgerald, Garrett, 1977, 1987, 1992, undated (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Gaughan, Michael, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - General Politics, circa 1970, 1976, 1978, 1985-1997, undated (Box 4, Folder 79-81, Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Goodman, Larry, 1991, undated (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Harvey, Richard, undated (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Haughey, Charles: General, 1982-1997, undated (Box 4, Folder 84, Oversize 22, Folder 8, Box 30, Folder 42)
    - Haughey, Charles: Visit to New York City, circa 1970, undated (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - Hederman, Carmencita, undated (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Higgins, Michael Daniel, 1992, undated (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Hill, Paul, 1984, circa 1990 (Box 23, Folder 18, Box 30, Folder 43)
    - Hillery, Patrick, 1989, undated (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Hume, John, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Hume, John and Pat, circa 1994 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Hume, John: General, 1970, 1990-1997, undated (Box 4, Folder 89, Oversize 22, Folder 9, Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Hume, John: Fordham Honorary Doctorate, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Hume, John: Irish Echo Man of the Year, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 19, Oversize 21, Folder 8, Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Individual Politicians: "A", 1992, 2002, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Individual Politicians: "B", 1976, 1983, 1992-1996, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Individual Politicians: "C", 1991-1992, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Individual Politicians: "D", 1962, 1988, 1996, 1998, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Individual Politicians: "E", undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Individual Politicians: "F", circa 1980, 1992, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Individual Politicians: "G", circa 1970s, 1992-1997, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Individual Politicians: "H", 1977, 1993-1999, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Individual Politicians: "I", undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Individual Politicians: "J", undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Individual Politicians: "K", 1989, 1996-1997, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Individual Politicians: "L", circa 1975-1977, 1989, 1995-1996, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Individual Politicians: "M", 1992-1994, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Individual Politicians: "N", 1993, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Individual Politicians: "O", 1992, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Individual Politicians: "P", 1983, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Individual Politicians: "R", 1991 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Individual Politicians: "S", 1976, 1985, 1995, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Individual Politicians: "T", 1990, 1995-1996, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Individual Politicians: "W", 1992, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Jordan, Neil, undated (Oversize 22, Folder 10)
    - Kelly, Nicky, 1992, undated (Box 5, Folder 21, Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Kenny, Enda, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Lemass, Sean, 1959, 1986-1987, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Lenihan, Brian, 1976, 1988, undated (Box 5, Folder 24, Oversize 21, Folder 9, Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Lynch, Jack, 1977, 1988, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - MacBride, Sean, circa 1970s, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Major, John, 1989, 1994, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Mallon, Seamus, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Markievicz, Constance, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Mayhew, Patrick, 1993, 1996, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - McAleese, Mary, 2002, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - McAliskey, Bernadette Devlin, 1977, circa 1980, 1990-1997, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - McDermott, Sean, undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - McGuinness, Martin, 1995-1997, undated (Box 5, Folder 35, Box 25, Folder 7, Box 30, Folder 44)
    - McSharry, Ray, 1983, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Molyneaux, James, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Moore, Richard, 1989, undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Mowlam, Mo, 1997, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - O'Bradaigh, Ruairi, undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - O'Malley, Des, 1992, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Paisley, Ian, 1993, 1996, undated (Box 5, Folder 41, Box 30, Folder 45)
    - Peace People, Committee Of (Betty Williams and Mairead Corrigan), undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Politicians and People - Heads and Portraits, undated (Box 33, Folder 23-24)
    - Politics General, undated (Box 20, Folder 2, Oversize 22, Folder 11)
    - Quinn, Ruairi, 1993, 1996-1997, undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Reynolds, Albert, 1988, 1992-1994, undated (Oversize 21, Folder 10, Oversize 22, Folder 12, Box 5, Folder 44, Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Reynolds, Albert - Maastricht, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 47)
    - Reynolds, Kathleen, 1992, 1996, undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Robinson, Mary: General, 1984, 1991-1997, undated (Oversize 22, Folder 13, Oversize 21, Folder 11, Box 5, Folder 46, Box 16, Folder 26, Box 32, Folder 45)
    - Robinson, Mary: Ellis Island, undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Robinson, Mary: Human Rights, undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Robinson, Mary: Irish Embassy Dinner, circa 1996 (Box 16, Folder 27, Folder 28)
    - Robinson, Mary: White House State Dinner, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 29, Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Ryan, Father Patrick, 1993, undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Spring, Dick, 1989, 1992-1997, undated (Oversize 22, Folder 14, Box 5, Folder 50, Box 16, Folder 30-31, Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Spring, Dick (with Orla Guerin) - Labour Party Echo Campaign Launch, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 46)
    - Thatcher, Margaret, 1992, undated (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Subseries II.D: Sports, 1975-1996
    This subseries contains photographs of prominent Irish athletes in addition to extensive photographic documentation of Gaelic football.
    - Bermingham, Mick, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Burke, John, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Cerebral Palsy Sport Ireland, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Charlton, Jack, 1991, undated (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Charlton, Jack and his boys, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Colleran, Enda, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Coughlan, Eamonn, 1996, undated (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Coughlan, Richard, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)